TAYLOR SANDERS

PROFILE

Dependable employee with 8 years experience in the creative restaurant industry. I believe I have a strong ability to trouble-shoot and problem solve in fast paced environments as well as excellent communication skills. I have many years experience in restaurant marketing, sales and customer service. I am dedicated to finding a new and exciting career that will benefit from my creative skill set and energetic drive.

EXPERIENCE

BARISTA, BOOM! COFFEE; ANCHORAGE, AK; MAY 2020- PRESENT A job centered around excellent customer service and keeping up in a very fast paced workplace.

PASTRY CHEF; SOUTH RESTAURANT + COFFEEHOUSE; ANCHORAGE, AK; APRIL 2018-NOVEMBER 2020

Manage daily Bakery Department duties, Organize and create menus for a number of upscale events, Inventory, Scheduling.

HEAD OF BAKERY DEPT., QUEEN CITY CATERING CO., CHARLOTTE, NC JANUARY 2017- AUGUST 2017

Manage daily Bakery Department duties, Creating desserts for the company, Handling all bakery catering orders, plating and helping to organize events.

PASTRY CHEF, AMELIE'S FRENCH BAKERY, ROCK HILL, SC MARCH 2016- JANUARY 2017

Worked in a fast paced environment to make a large variety of French pastries daily, Customer service, Inventory, specialty cake orders.

ASSISTANT MANAGER, THE COOKIE STORE, ROCK HILL, SC FEBRUARY 2012- JANUARY 2016

Handled all day to day operations with the business, Scheduling, Knowledge of proper cash handling procedures, Creating new menu items for the company, Inventory,

Customer service.

EDUCATION

FERRANDI PARIS, PARIS, FRANCE - PROFESSIONAL PASTRY COURSE, 2018

WINTHROP UNIVERSITY, ROCK HILL, SC- ARTS, 2016

18688 POTTER VIEW CIRCLE ANCHORAGE, AK 99516 | TSANDERS3515@GMAIL.COM